欢迎来到威廉斯堡餐厅
Welcome to the Williamsburg diner.
我叫麦克斯 因为我出生时
My name's Max, 'cause the hospital
医院不准我妈给我取名叫"我勒个去"
wouldn't let my mother name me "Oops."
整个夏天我都在外地
Uh, I've been out of town all summer.
有啥新料
Anything new?
新料的吗 我想想
Anything new? Let's see.
脸书公开上市
Well, Facebook went public,
爱德华·斯诺登转入地下潜逃
and Edward Snowden went private.
卡戴珊与侃耶生了个娃
Kim and Kanye had a baby, so now
所以又多了个不需要跟踪的卡戴珊家人
there's another Kardashian to not "keep up" with.
宝拉·迪恩下台 同性婚姻被通过
Paula Deen is out, gay marriage is in,
加州一名女老师下台
And a teacher in California is out
因为她跟她学生私通过
for letting her students get it in.
贾斯丁·比伯肇事逃逸
Justin Bieber got a hit and run,
克里斯·布朗也肇事逃逸
Chris Brown got a hit and run,
蕾哈娜被男友打[肇事]但还是没逃逸
Rihanna got hit and still didn't run.
奥普拉给了林赛·罗韩两百万
Oprah gave Lindsay $2 million,
迈克尔·道格拉斯舔阴得喉癌
Cunnilingus gave Michael Douglas throat cancer,
他给了全天下男性又多一个
and Michael Douglas gave guys everywhere
不为女人口交的理由
another excuse not to do that.
埃及疯了 亚曼达·拜恩斯更疯
Egypt went crazy, Amanda Bynes went crazier,
而国家安全局跟疯子前女友一样狂查我们手机
and the NSA checks our phones like a crazy ex-girlfriend.
德州讨厌女人 佛罗里达讨厌黑人
Oh, and Texas hates women, Florida hates blacks,
基本上大众看啥都十分不爽
And everybody hates everything with the exception
只看安吉丽娜·朱莉顺眼 她真的屌爆了
of Angelina Jolie, who is totally awesome.
我是说菜单 菜单上有啥新料理吗
I meant on the menu. Anything new on the menu?
完全不知道 我问问
I have no idea. Let me check.
卡洛琳 有啥我该知道的新料吗
Hey, Caroline, anything new I should know about?
英国王室金孙对女王笑了
The royal baby smiled at the queen.
我是说餐厅啦
I meant at the diner.
我们现在好像会洗叉子了
Oh. I think we're maybe washing the forks now?
我问问
Let me check.
麦克斯 你看 衣服一换
See, Max, one quick change,
我们就从聚酯衣可怜虫 变成强大自信女
and we went from polyester and pitiful to powerful and proud.
就跟超人一样
Just like superman.
人家超人是在电话亭里换衣变身
Except that superman changed in a phone booth,
而不是在写着"致电麦克斯 包爽"的厕所隔间
Not a stall that says, "For a good time, call Max."
你要是看那句话不爽 你干嘛还要写
Well, if you have a problem with it, why did you write it?
是因为我的眼线笔不够我再写上
'Cause I didn't have enough eyeliner to write,
"致电卡洛琳 包傻"
"For an interesting time, call Caroline."
厄尔 你看我们又穿上了
Look. Look, Earl, we're wearing our
麦克斯自制小蛋糕的制服了
"Max's Homemade Cupcakes" T-shirts again.
看到标识了吗
See the logo?
一直以来 我一直避免
Well, actually, I try never
直面你们两位的胸部区域
to look you ladies in the "chestal" area.
这样才能对你们无邪念
It keeps things on the up and up.
厄尔 你真是百万里挑一的好男人
Oh, Earl, you are one in a million, literally,
因为99万9千9百99个男人都只看我那个区域
'cause 999,999 men have only looked me in that area.
我得回家了
Well, I got to go home.
我疯狂在网上追《老公老婆不登对》
I'm binge-watching Dharma and Greg on Hulu.
我太想念在韩国长大的日子了
Oh, I missed so much growing up in Korea.
比如错过[想念]青春发育期吗
What, like puberty?
麦克斯 在我国家 我是中等身高
Max, in my country, I'm average height.
在我脑海里 我也还是富家千金
And in my mind, I'm still rich,
我的医疗保健计划也不是幼儿维他命丸
and my health care plan isn't Flintstones chewables.
谁有兴趣跟我们到后边
So who wants to go in the back
看看我们全新的小蛋糕店有多赞
and see how amazing our brand-new cupcake shop is?
收敛一点你的热情好吗 瑞秋·芮
Bring down the enthusiasm, Rachael Ray.
对 我们不能为新店开张的事兴奋过头
Right, we're not supposed to get all excited about this opening tonight.
上次就是搞的很隆重
Last time, we made a big deal,
结果店后来也不好
and the shop didn't do so well.
笑死人了 这就跟在核弹爆炸点
Ha! That's like saying the people
附近的居民说他们只是不太好一样
near the nuclear explosion didn't do so well.
女孩们 我很替你们高兴
Girls, I am so proud of you two,
东山再起 上马再战
getting back up on that horse.
我当年第一张爵士专辑卖不出去后
After my first jazz record didn't sell,
我就开始喝酒 吸毒 玩骚货的生活
I turned to a life of drinks, drugs, and loose women.
真是山穷水尽疑无路 柳暗花明又一村啊
Funny how sometimes things just work out right.
但你们怎么会是这个时间开张呢
But how can you be opening your cupcake window right now?
-现在半夜两点呢 -我们就开二到四点
-It's 2:00 A.M. -Our hours are 2:00 to 4:00.
我们主要目标客户是从酒吧玩完的人群
We're targeting the "post bars" demographic.
威廉斯堡醉酒男性
Drunk Williamsburg guys.
他们是我独自一人时的目标
That's my target when I'm by myself
也是我们新店的目标
And now my target at the new shop.
真是柳暗花明又一村啊
Funny how sometimes things just work out right.
我们对今晚的开张完全没有任何期待
We have no big expectations about the opening tonight.
今晚算是软开幕[试营业]
It's a soft opening.
软的跟硬的区别在哪啊
What's the difference between a soft one and a hard one?
要我展示给他看看吗
You want me to show him?
谢了 我们不需要
Thanks, but we're cool.
说真的 我只需不到一分钟
Seriously, it won't take me a minute.
不用了 奥列格
It's fine, Oleg.
告诉你们一声 我已经"硬"了
Just so you know, I'm already there.
做好准备 这房间被我们大改造了一番
Get ready, this room's had an amazing transformation.
-瑞秋·芮 -还行啦 随便吧
- Rachael Ray? - I mean, it's fine, whatever.
阿憨 进去前先闭上眼睛
Han, before we go in, close your eyes.
我想要你有最完整的体验
I want you to get the full effect.
对啊 我也想要绊倒你
Yeah, and I want to trip you.
-她开玩笑的啦 -她才不是开玩笑
- She's kidding. - No, she's not.
没错
Yeah, I'm not.
阿憨 我保证我不会让她绊倒你
Han, I promise, I won't let her trip you.
快闭上你的眼睛
Now, close your eyes.
-又咋了 -我刚才感觉到她要打我
-What? -Now, I thought she was going to hit me.
-她才没呢 -其实有啦
- She was not. - Yeah, I was.
够了 别搞这狗屁闭上眼了
Okay, no more blind eye bull crap.
快他妈的让我看那破房间
Just show me the damn smelly back room.
让我先关上灯 好营造更大的视觉冲击
Let me turn off the lights for a more dramatic impact.
叫屁啊 我又没干嘛
What? I didn't do anything.
是我干的
It was me.
他现在懂什么是"硬"了
He now knows what hard is.
我真不敢相信我的眼睛
I cannot believe my eyes.
我第一次见到你时也是同样的感觉
I felt the same way when I first saw you.
全部都是原创原装哦
Original tan, original tile, original too.
奥列格 你觉得如何
What do you think, Oleg?
不错
Nice.
不错 你就这么一句"不错"吗
"Nice"? All you got is "nice""
这里本来像是老鼠的主题公园
This place was like great adventure for rats!
它们还排队要进来咬我们呢
They were waiting in line to bite us.
卡洛琳 给他看看咬痕
Caroline, show them your bite marks.
-我不要 -不错
- I'd rather not. - Nice?
以前这里闻起来像是屎的坟场
It used to smell like the place poop comes to die.
又或者是死亡来拉屎的地儿
Or death comes to poop.
但你看这成果 我们亲手打造了这最棒
And look what we did! We created the greatest,
最酷最潮的小蛋糕店 我爱死了
coolest, chic-est cupcake shop, and I love it!
但也没啥激情啦 就软开幕罢了
But you know, no enthusiasm. Just a soft opening.
阿憨 能有这一切
And, Han, this was all possible
也是因为你不收我们租金
because you gave us the space rent-free.
什么免租 给我说说
Rent-free? Now, refresh my memory.
我什么时候说过这话
When exactly did I say "rent-free?"
在27号下午4点15分 你说
On the 27th, 4:15 P.M., you said,
"那个垃圾堆 你要免费拿去
"I don't care about that dump, you can have it for free.
还是一把火烧了我都无所谓"
burn it to the ground, for all I care."
我就知道学了英语 有一天我会遭报应
I knew learning English would come back to bite me in the ass.
已经有人来敲窗口啦
Soone's already knocking?
是很棒的兆头啊 麦克斯
That's a really great sign, Max.
是时候开店了
Time to open.
女孩们 我来为你们吹派对喇叭庆祝啦
Look, girls, I'm blowing this party horn for you.
谢了苏菲 但我们不想搞得太隆重
Thanks, Sophie, but we didn't want to make a big deal,
就是个软开幕而已
it's a soft opening.
我可喜欢软开幕[温柔前戏]了
Oh, I love a soft opening.
-你好啊 苏菲 -你好 奥列格
- Hello, Sophie. - Oh, hello, Oleg.
抱歉苏菲 害你们尴尬碰面了
Sorry, Sophie, about this uncomfortable meeting.
要是知道你会来给我们庆祝
If we had known you were going to surprise us,
我们就不会请他来了
We wouldn't have invited Oleg.
你们俩个分手那会我也在
Yeah, I was there when you two broke up
我现在还有PTSD呢
and I'm still suffering from PTSD.
"创伤后苏菲性闹腾大戏障碍"
"Post-traumatic Sophie drama."
才没有什么大戏呢
There's no drama.
最佳大戏的奖项得主是...
And the award for the best drama goes to...
绝非我们 对吧 奥列格
not us. Right, Oleg?
没错 我们现在是朋友
Yes, we're friends now.
女孩们 我出轨了
See, girls, I cheated on her,
所以她来砸烂了我的车窗
So she smashed in my car windows.
以及我公寓的窗户
and my apartment windows.
以及你的音响与平面电视
And your stereo and your flat screen.
以及我兄弟的平面电视与他女儿的电脑
And my brother's flat screen and his daughter's computer.
对啊 她吓到我了
Yeah, she surprised me.
她当时不应该在家的
She wasn't supposed to be home.
这些都是过眼云烟了 晚安 朋友
We got it out of our systems. Good night, friend.
晚安 朋友
Good night, friend.
对了 奥列格
And, Oleg?
真是根幸运的喇叭呀
That is one lucky horn.
宝贝 你们看 有客人
Honey, look. Look, some customers.
帅哥们
Hey, cool guys!
快过来这两姑娘的"软"开幕里吃点东西
Come over here and eat something from the girls' soft opening!
完全不是我计划中的广告方式
That is so not the way I would've gone,
但是无所谓了
But I'll take it.
你们好呀
Hello, hello.
你们这里有什么呢
What have we got here?
欢迎来到麦克斯自制小蛋糕
Welcome to Max's Homemade Cupcakes.
在英国我们叫它"仙女蛋糕"
In England we call 'em "fairy cakes."
叫这"仙女蛋糕" 我靠
Fairy cakes? Damn it.
为什么帅哥永远是基
Why are the hot ones always gay?
给 宝贝 整盘给我们吧
Here you go darling, give us the whole lot.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
美国运通黑卡
A black American Express card?
我手里多久没有握着黑的了啊
I haven't held a black one in my hands in years.
我还以为你从没手握过"黑"[阳具]的人呢
I would've guessed you hadn't held a black one ever.
抱歉 今晚刚开张 只收现金
Sorry, it's our first night. Cash only.
他感觉都嗑傻了啊
Oh, wow. He is really out of it.
-他嗑[上]啥了 -等会就是上我啦
- What is he on? - Besides me later?
不知道 但好嫉妒啊
Do not know, but am jealous.
我现在真的超嫉妒他啊
And now I'm really jealous.
他没事[人很棒]的
I'm sure he'll be fine.
我觉得他不只是很棒啊
Oh, I'd say he's more than fine.
他必须是我下一个男朋友啊
I'd say he's my next boyfriend.
罗兰 兄弟 醒醒啊
Roland, mate, wake up.
他停止呼吸了
He's not breathing.
叫不醒他 快叫救护车
I can't wake him, call 911!
叫救护车啊
Call 911!
大家冷静一下好吗
Let's all just calm down.
这种场面我见多了
I have seen this happen a lot.
有年暑假我去打工
One summer I had a part-time job
去吸毒所当紧急救护员
as a lifeguard at a crack house.
他很快就会醒来了
He'll come to in a second.
他死了
He's dead.
预言错了
Called that wrong.
麦克斯 昨晚死在我们小店门口的人
Max, the guy who died in front of our shop last night
生前是摇滚明星呢
was a rock star.
他跟凯特·摩斯约会过呢
He used to date Kate Moss.
无意冒犯 但跟凯特·摩斯约会
No offense, but dating Kate Moss
就像是英国法律一样
is like a law in England.
每个人满21岁的时候都得上她一次
Everyone has to do it when they turn 21.
他叫罗兰·格拉斯 有两张金唱片
His name was Roland Gass, and he has two gold records.
真不敢相信我没听说过他
I can't believe I've never heard of him.
我能信
I can.
你没事听的音乐是迪士尼音乐剧
Your go-to jam is the soundtrack from Newsies.
昨天还是摇滚明星 今天就挂了
Yesterday a rock star, and today he's gone.
世事难料啊
You never know.
所以我跟街角那家
That's why I ordered us breakfast
华丽早餐店订了早餐
from the fancy breakfast place on the corner.
你从荣誉学餐厅订了早餐啊
You ordered from Magna Cum Latte?
每天经过他的店 我都想着两件事
Every day when I pass by it, I think two things:
一 我好希望有把枪
one, I wish I had a gun.
二 有一天要跟它们订早餐 让它们送
And, two, someday I'm gonna order breakfast to be delivered
那个牛逼哄哄的牛角面包来
with one of their fancy-ass croissants.
谁知道我今晚会不会吸食海洛因过量
Who knows, tonight I could do too much heroin
然后莫名其妙死了
and die an unexpected death.
但好歹我也死於一件我妈爱做的事之下
But at least then I'd die doing something my mother loved.
你说得对 麦克斯 人生只有一次
You're right, Max. You only live once.
"人一"啊
Yolo.
你下次再说"人一"的时候 就是你的死期
And you only live till the next time you say "Yolo."
惨了 更多坏消息
Oh, no. More bad news.
我设置的麦克斯自制小蛋糕店谷歌搜索提示
According to my google alert for Max's Homemade Cupcakes-
你还设置对我们小店的搜索提示啊
You have a google alert for our business?
我只对"奥普拉裸上身"有设提示
I only have a google alert for "Oprah goes topless."
我不是说这一定会发生啦
I'm not saying it's gonna happen,
但如果真发生了
but I'm saying, if it does,
我会是第一个知道的人
I'm gonna be the first one to know.
网上都在传罗兰·格拉斯死在我们店门口
Look, it's online that Roland Glass died in front of our shop.
现在我手机也死了[没电] 死亡在传染啊
And now my phone just died. It's an epidemic.
奥列格 你还拿着我们小店的箭头在干嘛啊
Oleg, what are you still doing with the arrow from our shop?
你不是说挂好了吗
I thought you said that was hung.
我是说我鸟大[挂好了]
No, I said I was hung.
而现在也没法去帮你挂了
And I can't put it up now
你们窗口外有太多人了
with that crowd of people in front of your window.
有人在我们窗口外吗
There are people in front of our window?
兄弟 这里就是罗兰死的地方吗
Dude, is this where my man Roland died?
对啊 就这儿
Yeah, right over there.
那我要把这个放这 小熊放旁边
Then I'm gonna put this here next to paddington bear.
我在他上次演唱会上接到的
I caught this at his last concert.
然后还被人打[接]到了
And I also caught this.
兄弟 所以他就这么倒下了吗
So, like, what, dude? He just dropped to the ground?
他是先撞到这里 笑了 然后才倒下
Actually, he hit right here first, smiled, then fell.
他还笑啦 兄弟
He smiled? Dude.
麦克斯 能过来说两句吗
Max, can I see you over here?
我也感到很遗憾 但帽子很屌哦
Sorry for your loss. And dope hat.
谢谢 我在垃圾堆捡到的
Thanks. I found it in a dumpster.
麦克斯 你在干嘛
Max, what are you doing?
别告诉人家他有撞到柜台啊
Don't tell them he hit our counter.
我们得让蛋糕店跟这事情撇清关系
We need to distance ourselves from the entire event.
这对我们的新生意犹如灾难
This spells disaster for our new business.
兄弟 能来三打小蛋糕吗
Dude, can I get three dozen cupcakes?
也可能是成功
Or it spells success.
我有爆多朋友要来参加守夜活动
I have beaucoup friends coming here for the midnight vigil.
你的小蛋糕卖多少钱啊
How much are your cupcakes?
好贵啊
That's a lot.
兄弟 罗兰会希望是这个价的
Dude. Roland would've wanted it that way.
* 敲呀敲 敲开天堂之门 *
* Knock, knock, knocking on heaven's door *
摔倒之前 他的头撞到了这里
And he hit right here before he fell.
而摔倒时 他抬头看着我微笑
And as he fell, he looked up at me and smiled.
一脸满足和平静
Content. Peaceful.
多谢7块钱 只收现金
That'll be $7, cash only.
给你一张50的 能破开吗
Mira, can you break a 50?
麦克斯
Max!
什么事
Yeah, what do you need?
-一张50块 给人找钱 -好的
- Change for a 50. - Got it.
我是说 "好"可惜呀
I mean, why, God, why?
* 敲呀敲 敲开天堂之门 *
* Knock, knock, knocking on heaven's door *
给你四张10块
Ten, ten, ten, ten.
* 敲开金钱之门 *
* Heaven's door *
麦克斯 这里的小蛋糕快卖完了
Max, we're almost sold out in here.
-你去厨房多拿点过来 -好的
- I need more cupcakes from the kitchen. - Got it.
我马上回来
I'll come right in.
厄尔
Earl?
分成跟以前一样啊 我七你三
Same split as before. 30 cents on every dollar you sell.
真是白费劲
What a waste.
你知道如果我们卖大麻能挣多少钱吗
You know how much money we could make if we sold pot?
那个你也想加入呀 分成照旧哦
Oh, you want in on that too? Same split.
天啊 嬉皮士的广藿香味
Oh, man, that hippie patchouli smell
比这里本来的屎味还难闻
is worse than the poop was.
阿憨 小声点 人们在哀悼呢
Han, shh. These people are in mourning.
放尊重点
Show some respect.
我吗 居然让我放尊重点
Me? Me show some respect?
你们俩接下来要干嘛
What will you two do next,
在儿童医院的糖尿病科卖小蛋糕吗
sell cupcakes at the diabetes wing at the children's hospital?
你胆敢质疑我的真心
How dare you doubt my sincerity?
我曾两次亲自赶走
I personally have shooed a homeless man
一个要在悼念圣坛上撒尿的流浪汉
away from peeing on that shrine twice.
我不管27号下午的4点15分
I don't care what I may or may not have said
有没有说过什么话
on the 27th at 4:15 P.M.
你们的生意现在这么红火 我要收租金
Your business is booming, and now I want rent.
没门 那家伙本可以死在任何一个地方
No way, Han. That man could've overdosed anywhere.
但上帝把他送到我们窗前死 这是神赐之礼
But God made him overdose in front of our window as a gift.
没错 因为人生只有一次 所以我们接受这份礼物
And, yes, we are accepting that gift because you only live once.
人一
Yolo.
才不是 应该是"死一"
This isn't "yolo", It's "hodo""
人只能死一次
He only died once.
我真惊讶你们居然没把这句话印成T恤来卖
I'm surprised you aren't selling "hodo" T-shirts.
你怎么能这样说呢
How dare you again?
我们只是给需要安慰的人
We are simply providing some comfort food
提供一些安慰食物
to people who need comfort.
而且我要说 我们心怀着最崇高的敬意
And, I might add, we are doing it with the utmost respect.
* 敲呀敲 敲开苹果专卖店的大门 *
* Knock, knock, knocking on the Apple store's door *
够了 你们现在生意好得不得了
That's it, your business is booming,
我要收租金 200块
I want rent. 200.
一年吗
A year?
是一个月 对于这么漂亮的地方算是很低啦
A month, and it's a bargain for my beautiful space.
这地方漂亮是因为我们把它变漂亮的
This space is only beautiful because we made it beautiful.
对啊 给他看你的咬痕
Yeah, show 'em your bite marks!
麦克斯 我不要
Max, I'd rather not.
你们一个月要交租金200块
You will pay me $200 a month,
我意已决 你们做什么都没有用
and there is nothing you can do to change my mind!
-给他看你的咬痕 -好吧
- Show him your bite marks! - Fine!
她的屁股被老鼠咬了
A rat bit her ass?
好吧 那就收你们195块
Okay, 195.
不许收租 阿憨 当初我们可不是这么说的
No rent, Han. That wasn't the deal you made us.
这无关私人情谊 这是公事公办
This is not personal, it's business.
人家也想分一杯羹嘛
I want a slice of grief pie!
给他看你前面的咬痕
Show him your front bites!
不要 这太私密了
No! That's too personal.
-抱歉你不得不这么做 -我也很后悔
- Sorry you had to do that. - So am I.
-伤口愈合得不错嘛 -别骗我了
- It's healing nicely. - Don't lie to me.
我觉得把我们的花跟其他人的放在一起很不错
I think it's nice of us to add our flowers to the others.
以示尊敬
Shows respect.
说得好像这花不是你偷来的一样
You're acting like you didn't steal them.
麦克斯 有这份心就行了嘛
Max, it's the thought that counts.
而且我觉得从别人花园摘更便宜啊
And I thought it'd be cheaper to pull them out of someone's garden.
等等 悼念圣坛去哪儿了
Wait, where's the shrine?
瞧 阿憨把它挪到餐厅门口了
Look, Han moved it over to the diner door.
那个厚颜无耻的伪君子
That insolent charlatan!
不懂 但我支持你
Whatever that means.
* 敲呀敲 敲开天堂之门*
* Knock, knock, knocking on heaven's door *
姑娘们 你们能相信吗
Can you believe this, girls?
他居然赚死人的钱
He's cashing in on a man's death.
不带上咱们
Without us.
为了纪念他 今晚本餐厅供应
And in his honor, tonight we are serving
罗兰风味鸡排
Chicken a la Roland!
特别给大家打一个哀悼折扣 只需8块9毛5哦
At a mourner's discount of just $8.95.
看起来纯真的小蟋蟀转投黑暗面了
Looks like Jiminy Cricket turned to the dark side.
还有摇滚明星布丁哦
I also have rock star pudding.
这样不行 麦克斯 这是我们的悼念圣坛
Nope. No way, Max. This is our shrine.
把公仔熊拿过去
Grab a handful of bears.
我们要把死人的悼念圣坛挪回去吗
We're moving the dead guy shrine back?
等等 让我先为我的自尊烧根蜡烛
Wait, let me just light a candle for my dignity.
它在这里死掉了
It died here too.
麦克斯 你到底想不想成功
Max, do you want to be successful or not?
因为如果你想 把这些
Because if you do, grab one of these poems
一点也不遵守诗词格律的烂诗撕下来
that doesn't follow any of the rules of poetry,
粘回我们蛋糕店的窗口
and move it back to the cupcake window.
因为这笔死人财是属于我们的
Because this is our death.
我觉得你可能有点过于严苛了
I think maybe you're being a little harsh.
"在天堂摇滚 爱你的凯文"
"Rock out in heaven. Love, Kevin."
金句呀
That's gold.
哎呀 把蜡烛弄倒了
Oops, knocked over a candle.
没事 小火小火
Ooh, small fire, small fire.
烧到我的鞋了
Fire on my shoe.
如果我不把火弄灭 这就成了我的追悼会了
If I don't get this out, it's gonna be my memorial service.
大家快看
Look, look.
这两个女人在破坏逝者的悼念圣坛
Those girls are disrupting the shrine of a dead man!
大家快看 有蟑螂从餐厅里跑出来了
Look, look, a roach got out of the diner!
快踩死他
Quick, step on it!
嬉皮士们 快看 把大麻烟枪放下看一眼
Look, hippies, look! Put down those bongs and look.
她们为了自己的利益
They're moving the place where a man died
居然转移逝者死亡的地方
for their own financial gain!
这样做可不酷哦 伙计
Hey, that's so not cool, man.
-对啊 快回来 -呸呸呸
- Yeah, come on. - Yeah, boo!
-他才是那个不酷的人 -对啊 看他
- He's the not cool one. - Yeah, look at him!
罗兰·格拉斯是在我们可爱的
Roland Glass died a horrible death
小蛋糕店窗前可怕地死去
in front of our adorable cupcake window.
听见没 "可怕地 可爱地"
See? "Horrible, adorable"?
我脑子随便一转 想出来的词多押韵啊
That rhyme just came right off the top of my head.
你好你好
Hey! Hi. Hi.
他知道
He knows!
我曾告诉他不要在悼念圣坛上撒尿
I told him to stop peeing on the shrine
当时圣坛就是在这边
when it was still over there!
对不对
Isn't that right?
对 就是这个贱人
Yep. That's the bitch.
没错 我就是那个贱人
Yes! Yes! I'm the bitch!
这样可不酷 兄弟 把他扔出去
So not cool, dude. Let's get him out of here.
不要啊 住手
No! Stop!
那是我的钱包
That's my wallet!
住手 那不是我的钱包
Ooh, stop! That's not my wallet.
住手
Stop!
《摇滚年代》的演员们 住手
Cast of Rock of Ages, stop!
把他放下来 他很酷[自己人]
Put him down. He's cool.
即使衣着老土样子老气
Even with those clothes and that head.
我问你一句
I mean, really.
我们有这么渴望成功吗
Are we that desperate for success?
宁愿阿憨被人五马分尸也在所不惜
We'd let Han be torn apart?
我在想
I'm thinking.
-卡洛琳 -麦克斯 我说了我在想
- Caroline- - Max, I'm thinking.
现在没人来敲呀敲
Well, no one's knock, knock,
敲开我们的大门了
knocking on our door now.
现在外面安静得
It's more dead out there
比有人死在外面还要死寂一片
than when there was a dead guy out there.
我重新考量了我们今天的行为
I'm having second thoughts about how we behaved today.
我是说 我们怎么可以保住阿憨的小命呢
I mean, how could we have let Han live?
你们好呀
Hello.
为了表示感谢 我给你们带来了摇滚明星布丁
I brought you some rock star pudding to say thank you.
摇滚明星布丁 里面都有啥 药
Oh, rock star pudding. What's in it, pills?
破碎的梦想 还是带着泪痕的女生内裤
Broken dreams? Tear-stained panties?
卡洛琳
Caroline?
我可不像麦克斯那么好哄[上]
I'm not as easy as Max.
我七年级的时候 班里每个女孩都这么说
Said every girl in my seventh grade class.
我错了
Look, I was wrong.
不 阿憨 是我错了
No, Han, I was.
我们应该给你租金的
We should pay rent.
我不是在说租金
I wasn't talking about the rent.
租金 谁刚说租金了
Rent? Who said anything about rent?
我错了是因为当我说
I was wrong when I said
这无关私人情谊 这是公事公办
it wasn't personal, it was business.
在麦克斯阻止那群臭哄哄的嬉皮士
After Max stopped me from being torn
把我碎尸万段后
limb from limb by the smelly hippies,
我意识到 我们之间大部分是私人情谊
I realized, with us, it is mostly personal.
只有小部分要公事公办
And a little business.
小部分公事公办
A little business?
你的"事"能有多"大"啊
What other kind could you have?
麦克斯 不要嘲讽阿憨嘛
Max, let's not be hard on Han.
他不要我们的租金
He's giving us this space rent-free.
谁说不要租金了
No one said "rent-free."
我想到了一个公平的数字
I came up with a number I think is fair.
-25万 -是呀 真公平
- $250,000. - Yeah, sounds fair.
我记得这是你们俩第一家蛋糕店的目标
I remembered that was your original cupcake shop goal.
所以等你们达成那个目标 我们再说租金的事
So when you hit that amount, we can talk rent.
小憨憨 你真是太好了
Han, that is so sweet.
我不会把刚才她说的那句"硬憨"
And I'm not gonna ruin it by bringing up the fact
说出来破坏气氛呢
that she just said "hard on Han."
真的 阿憨 你真是太好了
Really, Han, it's so, so generous.
但我不知道我们承不承担的起
But I don't know if we're comfortable with it.
要不我们分你点股份吧
What if we offered you a small piece of the business?
我还是等租金吧 你们两个才是好姐妹好搭档
I'll wait for the rent. You two are good friends.
终于有女人愿意让阿憨"分一杯羹"
A woman finally offers Han a piece,
他却拒绝了
and he turns it down.
麦克斯 谷歌快讯
Max. Google alert.
奥普拉裸上身吗
Oprah's topless?
麦克斯 别想了 那是不可能的
Max, let that go. That's never gonna happen.
你这态度就肯定不可能了
Not with that attitude.
验尸报告表示 罗兰·格拉斯
No, the autopsy says Roland Glass
是被麦克斯自制小蛋糕噎死的
choked on a Max's Homemade Cupcake.
这下真的是灾难了
This is a disaster.
你的热情上哪去了 瑞秋·芮小姐
Hey, where's your enthusiasm now, Miss Rachael Ray?
这小店最牛逼了
This place is the balls!
要不了多久
And it's just a matter of time
那些心理变态的嬉皮士就会来
till those sicko hipsters are lining up
排队要买"噎死罗兰"的小蛋糕了
for "one of those cupcakes that killed that dude""
打开窗户 我们继续营业
Open the window! We're back, baby!
但我们也不能指望每周都有人死啊
But we can't count on a guy dying every week.
没错 我是有乐观积极的态度
I mean, I have a positive attitude,
但这也太过分乐观了吧
but that's too pollyanna.
不需要啊
We don't have to.
这才是这扇窗最棒的地方
That's what's so great about this window.
谁都不知道下一秒会发生什么事
Who knows what'll happen?
也是 我们也不必努力找生意
Right, and we won't have to chase business down
因为我们就在这条街上
because we'll be right here on the street
守株待兔
waiting for it to come to us.
麦克斯 我对未来的各种可能感觉好极了
Max, I feel so good about the possibilities.
昨晚是一张美国运通黑卡
One night it could be a black American express card,
而另一晚
And the--
麦克斯 是不是那个
Max, is it...
另一晚 是流浪汉
Other nights, it's a friendly little visit
友好地来拜访我们
from our homeless guy.